Today for our talk, we have
Professor Jake Williams
from Drexel University.
He is an associate professor
at information science
at Drexel University's College
of Computing and Informatics
in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
Dr. Williams has a background
in physics and math
with degrees from the
University of Vermont,
and his research leverages
a quantitative linguistics
perspective that applies math
and statistical methodologies
to analyze and improve
linguistic learning systems.
Following a one-year postdoc
appointment at the University
of Berkeley, studying
large language,
large-scale machine
learning in 2015,
Dr. Williams became a data
science faculty at Drexel
where he drove the foundation
of a DSMS program and develops
and instruct data
science coursework,
including natural language
processing with deep learning.
So welcome, and thank you for
coming today for your talk.
And you could do a quick
introduction of yourself
before you start.
Great.
Thanks so much.
I got the mic here.
Nice to see you all here.
Thanks for coming out, and
also for showing up online.
It's a pleasure to be here.
As was mentioned,
my name is Jake,
and my background is
in math and physics.
So the perspective that I'm
coming from towards this work
might be a little bit
different than the standard,
and that will be a theme
throughout the discussion.
The purpose of
this discussion is
to go through a relatively
long-term development, a project
that I've been working on.
And as mentioned, my background
is in quantitative linguistics,
which means my history
of focus on language
has primarily been to
develop general theories
and descriptions of
phenomena that you observe
with regards to linguistic
units, whatever those might be.
It's a statistical
approach which,
based on theories of
language generation
that are statistical in basis.
And over the course of
my time as a researcher,
I've explored and ventured
into language modeling itself,
and ultimately, into neural
networks as they approach
language modeling themselves.
And that's what brought
me here through quite
a bit of other work.
So if you look into
my profile, you'll
see a lot of different
subjects in either applied NLP,
like I said,
quantitative linguistic.
And neural networks is a
natural transition for me
into inferential work.
So let's get started.
Well, this is how we'll
start the conversation today.
It's not exactly how
we got here in my lab.
We came at this subject
from a different approach,
trying to think about
layer initializations
in neural networks.
And this subject
that we're discussing
as a front for this
talk is specifically
focused on transformer
architecture components,
the self-attention
component that's
pivotal to the success of
the transformer architecture.
And it focuses on the fact
that self-attention requires
a quadratic
comparison of vectors
in order to produce the feature
weights of those vectors needed
to model long-range
dependencies in text.
Commonly, parameters
for self-attention
are based on a
transformation matrix.
Two, usually, queries
and keys, that
are responsible for
dimensionalizing input vectors.
And I describe it this way
because generally speaking,
when you're at the point
of a self-attention layer,
you already have low
dimensional vectors.
But the parameters in a
standard self-attention layer
are changing the dimensionality
and the structure
of that dimensional space.
They are like an
embedding layer,
which is factorizing the
embedding dimensions.
This re-dimensionalization
is the primary means
by which self-attention
creates feature weights.
It really just computes
similarity in that shared space.
Large and similar inner
products really just
result in strongly
weighted features.
So it's up to that
dimensionalization
to produce good similarities
for whatever purpose
your prediction requires.
However, an alternative
strategy for future waits
might ask given a basis.
So in other words,
you're stuck with
your low dimensional vectors.
What is the optimal way to
convert those comparisons
of the vectors you're looking
at by a matrix transformation
to modify the vector
similarities that you
are stuck with that
correspond to the best
weights for features?
In other words, treat this
as a feedforward layer
to produce self-attention
weights as opposed to try
and transform to some basis that
produces good feature weights.
The use of this modified
self-attention mechanism
will be part and parcel
the substance of this talk.
It's worth noting that this
alternative mechanism is
entirely compatible with the
traditional dimensionalizing
version of self-attention.
In other words, you could
still change the dimension
and compute
similarities, and then
convert that with a
second feedforward layer
to produce optimal
feature weights.
This is not
exclusive in any way.
This is exploring how useful
that alternative prediction
of feature weights can function.
However, we'll avoid
the standard mechanism
for two reasons.
First, we have no solution
to the standard parameters
for self-attention
as an initialization.
And this will be discussed
at length in slides to come.
Likewise, it would create an
additional model complexity
that would muddle the
effects of the modified
form of self-attention
that we wish to study.
So having that
dimensionalization as a way
to produce good feature weights
would confuse whether or not
the feedforward computation
of feature weights
is functioning well.
There's a catch to
this, however, which
is that these
vectors that we use
for such a self-attention
layer better be good.
In other words,
their comparisons
must be consistent and
meaningful in the first place.
So to get it out
of the way, here
is an architectural
diagram for the relatively
simple near shallow architecture
pattern that we're using.
It doesn't seem like
there are many neurons
in a network of this
type, and that's
because all of the
activations are softmax.
Which means despite the fact
that the U-matrix, for example,
is an entire layer,
it's really just going
through a single
prediction non-linearity,
the softmax function.
So you can think about
this as essentially
a three-layer
network that might be
creating an encoder-decoder
kind of design.
Likewise, the difference
in presentation here over
self-attention, which is
parameterized by the matrix W
here, is intending
to show how a--
whether you consider it
the query or the key--
one vector is the pivot
for the comparison that
will produce the
feature weights,
which is then fed forward
in this model through W.
This is the case for
standard self-attention, too.
In other words,
you can reduce it
to a biprediction
diagram in this way
where a gray vector such as is
depicted here is that pivot.
The attention
distribution coming out
of the W matrix and
the softmax function
is indicated by the
vertical red bar
there, which weights the
block of vectors in black.
That includes the
pivot vector in gray,
which is then passed through a
feedforward layer often called
the values of a standard
self-attention matrix--
U.
Since we use U as
a way to reduce
the dimensionality
of the prediction
that we're trying
to make, we then
feed that forward
through another layer,
and then to output.
And that's essentially
the relative shallowness
that we're talking about here.
W is a self-attention
matrix, which
means there's really only
two layers in effect here.
And the activation
functions are strange.
And you might
wonder, for example,
why we're using a
different activation
function to softmax instead
of any of the dimensionally
independent activation functions
like a logistic function
or anything else.
And that's because we
have additional insight
into the softmax function
and the parameters that it
optimizes, which is very useful.
So let's talk about those
vectors first though,
before we get to
layer initialization.
Optimizing the keys and queries
of standard self-attention
bears substantial similarity
to token and word embedding.
This is because the
key and query matrices
have a common dimension
that they project to,
much like you'd see with the
factorization of an embedding
layer on its own.
Think word word2vec,
something like that.
Normally, there might be
multiple self-attention heads.
And because of the indeterminacy
in creating a different
dimensional space--
in other words,
there are multiple equivalent
reshufflings of those different
dimensions which will
produce the same output--
that indeterminacy is
something that we hypothesize
has bearing on what is now
referred to as the lottery
ticket hypothesis.
In other words, that multiple--
or this is the way
that I would state it--
but that multiple
different embeddings, which
produce different vector spaces,
can be leveraged in parallel
to create further robustness
for the model or in the way
that it's implemented that if a
random initialization doesn't do
that well, you can eliminate
it from the network,
and that subnetwork will do
just as well, even after it's
totally trained.
In other words, having
multiple clones,
self-attention heads, which have
no difference in the outputs
that they're trying
to predict, is
at the root of the
lottery ticket hypothesis.
And ultimately, that
invocation of the lottery
ticket hypothesis is really a
justification for eliminating
parameters through
substantial cost of training
are essentially wasted as a
result of random parameter
initialization.
You might ask
questions like, well,
what is a good initialization?
What is a good set of
word embeddings to use?
So how can a lottery
ticket hypothesis interact
with effects of randomly
initialized embedding layers
be avoided when
constructing language
models is another question that
is embedded in this discussion.
But we shouldn't say that
dimensionality reduction isn't
needed.
It's incredibly necessary.
For language modeling,
you absolutely
have to work with
reduced dimension
unless you're in a
very small vocabulary.
For example, like 26 Latin
characters or something
like that, like a wav2vec.
The inherent input dimension
of a large vocabulary model
presents many computational
interact abilities
when designing NLP systems,
something that you're probably
all very aware of.
Likewise, though, the
distance from embedding layers
to learning information,
the loss at outputs
puts them in a challenging
position to train.
It's really hard to learn
embedding layers because
of the indeterminacy
in the space
that you're trying to learn.
You could swap dimensions
and it's equivalent.
But the distance means
that they receive
learning information last.
This is a real
challenge, and it's
present in the history
of NLP and deep
learning to vanishing
gradient stuff.
And this is
exacerbated in the way
that we have to
actually learn embedding
layers in standard models where
we might modify learning rates
to be lower all the way back
at the bottom of a network,
to be gentle with
those embedding layers
and help them learn effectively.
But this is really
trouble because if we
had a good embedding
layer at the start,
those subsequent layers could
be much easier to learn.
So ultimately, in order to
approach this challenge,
we came along with a
discernibility hypothesis.
In other words, this
boiled down to the theory
that low dimensional
vectors, more than anything,
needed to be able
to discern features.
And that doesn't sound like
a very strong assertion.
And we started with a really,
really, really low bar
and assume that the most common
features needed to be the most
discernible features.
So if we're stuck
with a lower dimension
and we can't give
everything a one hot vector
to be told apart
very well, then we
might want to give the
more clear vectors which
have more dimensional
independencies to those features
which appear most frequently
and could stand to confuse
models the most.
This hypothesis led us directly
to develop the bit-cipher
algorithm, which is really just
a scheme for assigning vectors
of 0's and 1's.
Nothing too crazy in terms of
what we're attempting to do.
In the figure at right here,
the order of vector assignment
is by row from top to bottom.
And this is on a 5 dimension,
5 bit-vector system.
The first 5 from bottom
are those one-hot vectors.
Past that point, you'll
see two-hot vectors,
but they're a little
bit less darkly shaded,
indicating the way that we
actually utilize the system.
In other words, we normalize
them to have unit sum.
What I hope you
can see from this
is that the bit-cipher algorithm
generalizes one-hot vectors
to low dimensions.
And as a result, we can work
from a very sparse feature set
and explore dimensionalities
as a controlled phenomenon.
And this assignment is
incredibly naive, too.
That's the other thing that
I want you to see, as well.
That this discernibility
hypothesis
does not create any meaningful
correlations between tokens
that behave similarly.
So if you've got the upper
and lower case of a word,
their vectors aren't going
to capture those similarities
according to the bit-cipher.
It's really just going
to try and make sure
that those features
are distinguishable
in a low dimensional
space and that the most
distinguishable
features are those
which appear most commonly.
This was enough to do a
surprising amount of work.
So with some scheme
for a deterministic low
dimensionalization
procedure, we were then
able to utilize this
solution that we had actually
developed previously.
So this was actually the real
motivator for a lot of the work
that you're seeing today, while
it might seem like it's just
a checkpoint in the middle.
Provided bit-cipher
produces decent embedding.
We can ask, can other layers
be non-randomly initialized?
In other words, without
gradient descent
or back propagation or other
gradient-based iterative
algorithms.
This equation came about
from analysis of word2vec
with the original softmax
activation function.
And much like
other articulations
of the word2vec,
family of embeddings
came up with differential
solutions that
depended on
co-occurrence matrices,
we formalized this
as a question.
Is there a way to take a
co-occurrence matrix, F,
in this equation here, and
convert it with some weights,
some denominators by
rho into something
that warms up a single
layer feed forward
in a neural network.
And ultimately, this k minus 1
over k term here and this sum
is really just
expressing something
like conditional probability.
Like conditional probability,
because k minus 1 over k
is a wrinkle that says that
as the number of features
increases, in other
words, the context window
increases in a
block transformer,
then the warm
start that we could
apply to start off a neural
network without a randomness,
randomness entirely
determined by the vectors
underneath nearing whatever
direction it's going.
All we have to do is
compute some co-occurrences
between inputs and outputs.
And I don't mean necessarily
standard co-occurrences
that you might have learned
about a long time ago, which
depend on a radius.
I mean, whatever your inputs
are, whatever your outputs are,
you take their sum
of outer products
and you get a co-occurrence
matrix of inputs and outputs.
And that can then be utilized
to initialize your layer
in that neural network to be
vastly more performant than what
you'd get by a random
initialization.
This was a strong
motivator for us.
This was just for a
single layer model,
but it depended on the softmax
function for activation.
And the softmax function,
as an activation function,
we knew is also necessary
for self-attention features.
And this meant that if we
could put self-attention
into some kind of a standard
form with this equation,
just like a single layer, then
we could apply the same solution
with one catch.
That catch is
specifically that we
don't know what the targets
are for self-attention.
There is no target vector y.
The thing that you're
trying to predict,
which position is
the one that you
want to weight most strongly.
And so in order to
apply this solution
for a self-attention model, we
had to do some more analysis.
And that's in the reference
number 1, which is all the way
back up in the first slide
if you want to see it.
But that derives a
differential criterion,
an analog for the
single layer solution
that tells us what the targets
of that kind of self-attention
actually are.
The hidden targets, the weights
that you're trying to create,
which really are just
about making sure
that the layer
above self-attention
has some unsurprising
things coming towards it.
The self-attention layer
is really just trying
to massage the vectors,
so that way they
look like something that the
next layer above expects.
Aside from that, though, it's a
much more in-depth conversation.
The point, though, is that for
the model in this picture here,
we can now start off with
vectors x that are not random.
We can use those vectors x
to initialize non-randomly
the parameters in w, the
self-attention matrix,
and then use that
going up the network
to initialize the
parameters in u since it's
just a feed forward layer
with whatever self-attention
is giving it his weights.
And then whatever that
produces, the hidden state h,
we can use that with the actual
targets after the output layer
to warm up the matrix O.
And you might say OK, well,
how did you figure out what
those hidden targets are?
Like you had to have an output
for the U matrix to try and hit.
That too is something
that the bit-cipher
can provide in the form
of label embeddings.
In other words, low
dimensional targets
of the thing that is downstream
that you're trying to hit
the language model's output.
So similarly, we can
warm start the U matrix
in terms of those
bit-cipher label embeddings.
So in this view, the aim is
to show how simple and general
the single layer softmax
activated solution is to apply.
It's really just no more
challenging than computing
conditional probability
given inputs and outputs.
It's fast.
It's something that
you can distribute
in terms of processing.
And it's very, very general.
So this is essentially
the process
that we're using in order to
warm up the W and U matrix.
There's the U matrix there.
Starts out as zeros.
So in other words, nothing.
No random values,
no weights anywhere
over the data, which
is just borrowing
the dimension of this
gigantic Y matrix that
has all of the targets in
it for the entire data set.
We simply just take
the outer products
of whatever the hidden state
the input to that layer is,
assuming that the
lower layers beneath it
are also warmed up with whatever
the targets for that layer are.
Following that, it's really
just about normalization
and a logarithmic
transformation.
And that logarithm
really just emerges
as a result of being an inverse
to the exponential function,
which is a part of softmax,
pretty much all of softmax.
And that's really
what brought us here.
So what does warm
starting a network do?
This is going back to before
we had the bit-cipher algorithm
for dimensionality reduction.
And we started out
by just saying, OK,
if we take a simple, simple
language model that only looks
at a radius of traditional
co-occurrences as features,
we can concatenate those
vectors and feed them forward
for a language model's output.
A completely random start, a
cold start to a language model
is really just the size of
the vocabulary in perplexity.
And those three lines here
for a few different radii
are demonstrating that point
with the point all the way
at the top left-hand corner
of this figure, cold starts.
In any of those cases when
the warm start is applied,
the perplexity is immediately,
automatically lower.
And furthermore,
the trajectories
that the updates follow continue
in the same learning rate
and the same time
to perform better
than models that
were started cold.
If you have an early
stopping criterion,
similarly, early stopping
will more than just generally
engage first.
And with a higher perplexity.
So this was the first
indication that we
had figured out something
that's very useful.
I saw some folks on Slido
say they're confused.
They're asking, are we talking
about an alternative approach
to self-attention?
We are.
And that's all the
way back at slide 1.
And it is the premise of
this whole conversation.
So here in this modified
version of self-attention,
you might normally expect to
do a comparison of your inputs,
the matrix X. Whatever
your inputs are,
they might be a whole
block of vectors
or they might be--
this is self-attention.
It's not cross-attention where
you have different vectors
that you're trying to attend.
And forgetting about
the values, which
for us is the U matrix,
the keys and queries which
are the parameters
for self-attention
are in the middle.
They're in between the two
copies of the inputs X.
Each of those, you can view
as some kind of a projection
down to a dimension
where they can interact.
And this is necessary
for something
like cross-attention,
where you might
have different
dimensionalities like X1 and X2
in two separate
groups of vectors
if you're doing something
like machine translation.
That's not necessary to
think about when you're just
looking to do a standard
language model that
has to predict the next output
according to the inputs, which
are also outputs from
previous iterations.
Two insights here.
One that multiplying
the key and query
matrices Wk and Wq is just
another parameter matrix that's
implied.
There aren't two
parameter matrices
there in the middle
for self-attention
in any effective way.
There is a common
dimension of comparison,
and that kind of just
moves stuff around.
It creates degrees of
freedom so that optimization
can figure out what's the best
weighting from comparisons.
But the softmax
function is strictly
operating on similarities
of that comparison space.
It's not doing anything
with those similarities.
It's just softmaxing them.
It's just activating them.
So if it was a big similarity,
it's a big attention value.
In this equation,
there's no transformation
happening before those vectors
are multiplied together.
Inner products.
So those vectors
better be good vectors
that you're starting with, X
and X transpose, the same thing.
They better be vectors
that are comparable.
They can't be vectors
from cross-attention
where you're trying to translate
from one language to another
and they just don't
inner product.
They're different dimensions.
You could force it through
if they were two differently
trained embedding layers.
And they had the same
dimension with this mechanism.
And if you didn't, you could
put those key and query matrices
back in between the 2x
vectors, x blocks of vectors.
But a lot of what's going
on here in this talk
is trying to simplify and make
more efficient the architectures
that we need and the
mechanisms that they
utilize given what we know
about how language functions.
And that's a
critical piece there.
We have assumptions
that we can make.
If all we're doing
is autoregression,
we don't need cross-attention
dimensionalization in between.
That'll be the theme.
In other words, that
can we use knowledge
that we have about
the way language
functions to design better
versions of architectures
that meet the needs of language
instead of being simply general?
Just good.
This is important.
So if there are any questions
here, it's a good time.
We are there and there.
So we just talked briefly.
This was for language.
I'm thinking about
language models.
It's a really simple
language model.
There's no
self-attention here yet.
This is really just
evaluating that a warm start
in either the blue,
green, or purple case
does better than
its partner, which
is a cold start of
the same architecture,
same hyperparameters--
orange, reddish, and brown.
So three different models,
regardless of how long
your context is
in each case here,
we see that a model which has
a non-random initialization
by the equation presented
two slides back from here
starts a network of with
a much lower perplexity.
The requirements to apply this
solution to a feedforward layer
of parameters is simply
that your inputs should not
have negative values.
That's really all we
have to worry about.
So it becomes really easy to
ask questions like, well, what
happens when you apply
this to other data
with non-negative values?
Well, there's one
little catch that we
had to think about
here in this case.
And that is with the
bit-cipher or one-hot vectors,
we're controlling the
norms of the inputs
with standard embeddings,
with MNIST, for example,
when you're trying to
predict a handwritten digits
0 through 9 value.
You don't get to assume
necessarily that all inputs have
the same norm.
You can normalize the inputs,
but it doesn't necessarily
make sense to normalize
them to one when you're
looking at images, for example.
They're non-negative.
They have 0 through 255,
for example, in MNIST.
And as a result, we
can put these data
through that same warm start.
Now, one little caveat
here I've alluded
to about the norms of
vectors is that we don't
know what that value of k is.
In other words-- let me go back.
You could look at
it here or here.
That's the number of
features per prediction,
which if you're looking at
unit normed word vectors,
is however big your context
window is, because they all
have unit norm and
there's k of them.
But if you're looking
at just an image,
it's not clear if it's a
composition of multiple vectors,
if it's one vector, and how many
it is, if it is a composition.
It just has a norm.
In application to
data like that,
that is what k becomes, the
average norm of an input.
And I'm regretting not
putting a graph in this,
but the paper that discusses
this shows that in the MNIST
data set, the exact
optimal value of k
is the average
norm of the inputs,
however you've
preprocessed them.
And that's how we generally
apply this rule when
we're warm starting systems and
we don't have unit norm vectors.
And it was learned from studying
this model's application--
this solution's application
to non-linguistic data.
But as mentioned, the purpose
was always towards language.
So longer context
windows in principle
should provide models with more
information than shorter context
windows.
This means one should
expect that models
perform better when context
window length is longer,
theoretically.
And this is
essentially the reason
for why self-attention
was initially developed.
Researchers wanted to improve
language models and context
windows, providing more
information were seen as the key
to that.
In other words, the more
features, the more information,
the more flexibility a model
can have and expressivity.
However, without
feature weights,
models didn't simply get better
with long context windows,
and feature weights
and self-attention
were hypothesized to be needed.
And this was proven back in
2017 with the transformer
architecture.
In moving towards
self-attention and transformer,
though, the primacy of the
transformer architecture's block
context model casts a shadow
over the use of other context
models.
So, for example, if
I were to ask here,
is it clear to everyone that the
standard self-attention block
model of context is different
than the traditional notion
of co-occurrences,
which use a radius that
is not positionally anchored?
It is the context model,
the positional anchoring
of the block context model
that gives it its information.
It is not in all
likelihood anything else.
Now what you do with that
context model matters.
You can't just take
those vectors in a block,
add them together, and expect
a feed forward to do well.
That's where self-attention
is needed in order
to figure out which vector needs
the best weight, most weight.
So what you'll also see
in the architectures that
are based on what
I've already presented
is that we're
interested to explore
how different models of
context for language models
can be integrated in general,
because they each provide
different information.
And we all know that the
standard transformers block
model of context requires a
ridiculous amount of information
and data in order to
become effectively trained.
So the current spate of
contexts that we use,
top there might be the standard
transformer context that
has a fixed positional block.
And it takes the
first 10 tokens,
for example, the second 10
tokens, and the third 10 tokens
each in different blocks.
And each of those is a group
of contextualizing vectors.
The second one there that you
see with the r as a subscript
is a radial model because
those do different things.
In other words,
rather than assume
you're looking at the first
10 or the nth 10 features,
you pick a radius.
And you say, what are the last
r features, the last r vectors?
That can also have an
attention distribution,
a self-attention
distribution according
to the exact same model
that's being presented.
It produces an entirely
separate context
in the state, whatever
you want to call it,
which can be conjoined
with the block model
to articulate features and be
given to an output layer that
knows what to do with them
when each has different values.
The concatenation of those
different context models
keeps the information separate.
So the output layer can decide
which portion of the context
is useful for the prediction.
This last one is getting really
traditional at the bottom.
It's what I refer to
as a document model.
If you've ever implemented
something like a Naive Bayes
classifier or a term frequency
inverse document frequency
model, that's essentially
what a document model is.
Add up your vectors,
you get something.
Is it going to be the best
for predicting the next token?
Absolutely not.
However, it's always different.
And what that means
is that even if you
wrap to the next block between
the radial and the document
models, you have a unique
context vector, even if you're
looking at the exact same block
because the document has grown
and the radius just says,
what are the last three?
What are the last 10?
As a result, when you
incorporate different models
of context, you
don't really have
to say that there's a
finite context window.
It might not be very
good to make predictions
past the first block, but
that might be about how much
data you've used,
and it might be
about the hyperparameters
for each one of those models
that you're applying.
In other words, the radius
and the block size like usual.
So far, the only embeddings
that I've suggested
are from this
bit-cipher algorithm.
And as I've
expressed there, they
don't capture any
useful similarities
between similar tokens.
The bit-cipher
algorithm, it doesn't
care if you're looking at the
uppercase or lowercase version
of a word.
It doesn't see them as
bearing any similarity,
even though there might
be used very similarly.
So how can you
utilize the bit-cipher
to create vectors
for tokens that
have meaningful
similarities between words
that are used similarly?
And this is just backing off
to the traditional methods
once again taking co-occurrences
of bit-cipher vectors
with whatever is there
at the middle or center
of a co-occurrence model.
Normally, if you think
about one hot vectors,
a co-occurrence matrix is
really just the same thing,
except now we just
have smaller vectors
with different dimensions
on, so to speak.
And we normalize
after concatenating
these blocks of different
radii from the bit-cipher
to match the original input
requirements that we discovered
for the warm start solution.
And that enables us to use
these just like we would
the original bit-cipher
vectors, except now,
just from the usual
co-occurrence statistics,
you'll see that capital
word and lowercase word
have a lot of common usage.
And you know this works because
you've seen co-occurrences
for a very long time.
And while they
might not normally
be useful in our applications
these days with deep learning,
they can be imparted through
the bit-cipher algorithm
to prescribe vectors as well.
So here's where things
start paying out in terms
of speed and efficiency.
If you only have one
layer of self-attention,
then that means
that you don't need
to worry about whatever weird
expressive stuff is happening
that similar inputs
might have slightly
different hidden states.
Since that first layer is just
a set of static word embeddings,
the self-attention
layer is working off
of static word embeddings.
And that means
each pair of words
have a fixed comparison
given static word embeddings.
And that means if you want to
compute the quadratic features
of self-attention, you can just
pre-compute them and pull them
from memory.
This caching of
vector comparisons
is essentially reducing the
self-attention layer's cost
from quadratic to
linear, since those
values that we're
using to weight
the vectors for the
feedforward layer
no longer require
comparison across the block.
They're already compared.
So when our vectors are static,
which is at inference time,
and if we're not learning
the embedding layers
parameters with iterative
differential updates,
then not only do we have
to not track gradients
for the embedding
layer, but we don't even
have to compute the
vector comparisons.
We can pre-compute them
and just load them,
which is much, much faster.
So we can reduce a lot of--
all the inference
and training costs.
Not all of the training costs,
some of the training costs,
because if we want to
update those vectors,
then we can't assume
cached comparisons.
But it's a huge cost savings.
This means that we can train
these self-attentive feedforward
unit models very quickly and
with good initializations.
But there are some other
things that we immediately
observed while
developing these models,
and that is the lack of
randomization produced models
which were quite effective
even on small data.
Now it doesn't mean that
training on small data
will let you generalize
to everything else that's
out there in the world.
In other words, training
on a small data set
might produce a model which has
a surprisingly low perplexity
on its training set.
But it doesn't mean
that you're going
to be able to generalize and
have a language model that's
talking well from just hearing
a couple of thousand tokens.
It does mean it will know
that couple of thousand tokens
very well, very quickly.
But there is a challenge with
using self-attention still,
and that is the fact that
the block model of context
often is not fully utilized
since many documents are
shorter than long context
models or long context windows.
And these days, there are
exceptionally long context
windows.
I'm not even
talking about those.
Many of the language modeling
benchmarks simply don't even go
out to 1,000 words when it comes
to contexts and you're looking
at a document to predict.
So this has been a
problem for a while.
And it means that
if you're going
to pad your short
documents, you're
going to waste a lot of
prediction on those paddings.
A lot of computation gets lost
just for null information,
essentially.
And the way that this is
often relieved in some groups
and to great effect is
by packing long contexts.
So, for example, if you've got
a 100,000 token context window,
most documents will not
be 100,000 tokens long.
What do you do with the rest of
that long context if you want
to use 1,000 tokens
of good training data?
You fill out the other 99,000
tokens with a bunch of other
random documents that don't
belong anywhere near the first
one.
That's called packing.
Packing can be utilized without
impacting different documents
with each other, without
contaminating the information
between documents.
And that takes a lot of
work, but it can be done.
However, there are different
strategies that we could employ,
different engineering
tricks that we
could employ to make our
operation of self-attention
more effective at any
length of document
without having to deal
with this packing problem.
And that comes about by
dynamically changing the context
length from some
maximum value, that's
what you would normally set.
Just use the context
that you have.
But you still have
to create batches
if you want to train
models quickly.
And what that means is that
there's still some padding
if you use this approach.
But you can pad those short
documents to set lengths.
Batch short documents together,
batch long documents together.
This means that we don't need
to pack documents together
to make use of a
long context window.
When a document is long, you
can let its context be long.
When a document
is short, you can
put it with other
short documents
and just use a subset of those
self-attention parameters.
And with traditional
self-attention parameters, keys
and queries, it would
never be a subset
because it's a low dimensional
that, that matrix provides.
With this modified
self-attention,
though, there's a different
shape to the weight matrix.
And that's why it's a
subset of those parameters
that we have to utilize.
And that might be something
worth discussing afterwards.
In other words, how
does the difference
in shapes of
dimensionalities between this
and the standard self-attention
weights shake out?
But we want to get to a
different point for the sake
of this conversation.
What is a model like
this useful for?
That should be a question
that you're asking.
It's a question that
we've been asking.
We're not entirely
certain yet how
an extremely large
model like this
will function on trillions
of tokens, for example.
In other words, can you
expect the same kinds
of outcomes like a
ChatGPT kind of thing
from some of these models?
Human interaction and
RLHF all the rest of that.
Though it's something that
we're considering, but also
at different scales
too, since those
are performant on
their own as well.
But for what?
So the point is, is that
from what we've stress-tested
into the billions, models
can be trained very quickly
on a relatively
small GPU in ways
that we expect when we
cache vector comparisons,
we see really big
speed-ups. When
we don't cache
those comparisons,
you see all of the growth
in computation time
that you would expect from
longer context windows.
This one here,
though, we're trying
to make it really,
really, really small,
the one called potato.
And that's because
we want to see
if we can train a model
from scratch since on very
little data, these models
can fit effectively
with the initializations
that we've developed.
And with the purpose of
starting from scratch,
starting with no data, we're
thinking about edge computing
cases where we could deploy a
language model with a microphone
so that a person can talk
to it and just train it
from their own data, train
it from their own speech
to understand their speech.
So between these,
we've explored a lot
of different configurations,
trying to consider similarities
to what some standard
configurations might look like.
A couple thousand tokens
in a context window,
for example, to look something
like a GPT-2 style model.
Thinking about bit-cipher
embeddings that are 500
dimensional or 1,000 dimensional
to be something like a GPT-2.
That's again pointing towards
the big/large category of models
that we've experimented with.
Beyond that, we haven't
really touched those scales
because our first objective is
not to make big, big language
models and train chatbots.
We want to know, what can
we do with a small model
since this is a relatively
unique capability?
So what does training look like?
To the best of our ability so
far, it's kind of hard to see,
but the first step is
that warm start where
you train the bit-cipher and you
take a couple of splits of data
and you compute that warm start
for the self-attention layer
and the feed forward layers.
In this case, which
is really just using
a 100 million token data
set from the baby language
model challenge, which
has as an objective
to see what language models
can do on a relatively
human scale of data.
In other words,
100 million tokens
is something that a person might
hear in 10 years of their life.
In 10 years of life, people
become pretty proficient
speakers.
And can a language model
be trained at that scale?
The second stage after
the warm start happens
is where the majority
of training time
occurs, and yet is
also where training
operates the most quickly.
At this stage, we find that
freezing vectors is important.
One, because it means that
we can train much quicker.
So we can have the
subsequent layers optimized
beyond their warm
starts very, very fast
using that vector caching,
the vector comparison caching
to avoid the quadratic
costs of self-attention.
This articulates the
parameters in the middle layers
of the model for taking
100 million tokens
and making five passes over
the data here a lot quicker
than any of the other stages.
And the comparison
that you'd make to this
is the training time once those
embedding layers are unfrozen,
where everything slows down
to the normal speeds, where
you have to do all of your
vector comparisons on the fly
since you can't assume that the
same comparisons will always
result in the same numbers
since model parameters might
be updated.
This is the best procedure
that we've figured out so far.
And in order to make
those vectors update,
we find that learning rates
have to be adjusted dynamically
inside of the
network like normal,
and that the embedding
layers are really
tough to make progress on.
And you'll notice
here in this picture
that the slowness and the lack
of stability, for example,
in learning the embedding layer,
once it had been prescribed
earlier, makes it really hard to
train over the entire data set
compared to five passes, for
example, in the middle phase
when the middle and upper
parameters are being updated
still with backpropagation.
And the other thing
that I would highlight
before leaving this slide is
in phase 1, how the warm start
saturates pretty quickly?
So if you have 100
million tokens,
you really only need to apply
the warm start to something
like maybe 10 million
tokens, not that much more.
You don't see that much gain
from that much more data.
That's not a bad
thing, because it
means that we
don't have to apply
that process for any longer.
I mean, it would be great if it
gave us all of the optimization
that we could hope for,
but it's not something
that we could necessarily
expect since it's just
an approximation of where
the parameters are headed.
So on the back of an
envelope, thinking about
how the systems
that, that example
was trained on as compared
to other examples that
are out there.
And thinking about models
that are kind of similar size.
We're talking about a 12
gigabyte gpu, a relatively small
single chip, specifically when
referring to these training
times.
So that's 12 gigabyte gpu.
Just working off of eight chips,
each having a roughly four
times the scale and
comparing to this time
that it took to train something
with maybe an additional order
of magnitude, although
we have trained models up
to around 50 million
parameters to which
is getting towards GPT-2 scale.
We see training times
that if we scaled up
to the relatively large
systems that present us
with how much work we should
expect to have to do for a model
that large, we can expect to
be able to train much faster.
But as mentioned,
the initial objective
here is not to simply figure
out how well we can do something
that's being done well already.
It's to figure out what these
alternative strategies are
useful for, since they give
us access to different regimes
of model scale as effective.
So as mentioned, we've gone
to relatively large amounts
of data.
I wouldn't really call
them big data at this time,
even though just
a couple of years
ago, a billion tokens would be a
relatively large amount of data.
It's really just a stress
test at this point, gives us
something like, do
we continue to see
models getting better as we
continue to give them more data?
Do we continue to
see models getting
better as we continue to give
them longer context windows?
And the answer to both of those
questions is absolutely Yes.
So nothing is telling
us that we can't
train bigger models with these.
But will those
bigger models be as
good as a standard
self-attention model?
I don't know.
It's a different
self-attention parameter
matrix than what you see in a
standard self-attention model.
You could integrate the two.
And in theory, that
should be overkill
because you'd have more
parameters and more power
through them.
And we can see
from this work that
the alternative
self-attention parameters
are reasonably effective.
We're getting close to time.
So I'll go quick
through these since this
is the work that we're
approaching right now.
And this is the idea
that we're seeing
as a use case for such
a model like this.
In other words, no pre-training.
Just training on the
target data, whatever
the data of interaction are.
And this example, you'll
see that this relatively
small or precision
language model just
needs to predict whether or not
a light should go on or off.
A lamp that listens with
a microphone and a switch,
and you can use that
switch to train the lamp.
So that's the goal here.
Can pre-training be eliminated?
And we want to
anticipate whether or not
you're going to flip
the light on or off.
That's the task that we're
going to try and approach,
or that rather, we're
currently approaching.
There's a few different
processes that
integrate into this approach.
There has to be a
microphone that's listening
to you, recording audio.
There has to be a
transcription algorithm.
And we use wav2vec at
this point because there's
a very small version of
it that's character-based.
And as a result doesn't even
require you to use consistent
or it does require you to
use consistent language,
but it doesn't even
require you to use words
since it's strictly phonetic.
There has to be--
and this is the bread
and butter of what's
going on here, a process which
anticipates what you want.
And that process is responsible
for creating good training data.
So this is a smart data
collection algorithm
that figures out when
you flip the switch,
is that the target for
something that you just said?
Is that the transfer
learning objectives
from text that was transcribed
that it anticipates you want?
Following this, there's
also two other processes,
one which operates on
a different time cycle,
and that's training.
So always train a model,
always be training a model.
Whenever there is new
data is essentially
what that fourth process says.
And the last one is operation.
In other words, if
you flip the switch,
there has to be a process
which operates the light bulb.
It always has to be a lamp
in order to be useful.
It always has to be able
to just be a switch.
However, that operation
process likewise
needs to see a directive
from the anticipator.
If the language model
predicts that you just
said a thing, that means
you want there to be light,
that operator then needs
to receive the signal
from the anticipator and
execute the directive.
If the user then though
within some time scale
changes the switch back
after the model created
a prediction that
was bad, the operator
is also responsible for issuing
a correction to the anticipator
to correct the training data.
What this looks like as a
process is in this diagram here.
And you can see the
flow here from stage 1,
a verbal command maybe gets
recorded, transcribed, turned,
in a text.
And if there's no model
that's yet trained,
that text is just stored as
data along with any directives
given by the user in the form of
a light switch going on or off.
Once there's any data,
the learning process
says, OK, time to
train a language model
and integrate it
with these targets.
Once a model is
done training, it's
sent over to the anticipator
who is responsible for using
the language model.
That small language
model then is now
empowered to make
predictions every single time
it receives a text command.
And those predictions are
sent to the operator, which
then does whatever it's told.
And the last thing
that can happen,
step 6 is if the wrong
prediction was made
and the user fixes it by turning
off the light because they
didn't want the light
on, that corrects
the data that was transcribed.
And the next model
which is trained
will be able to
avoid that problem.
And there's some
dialing this in,
in terms of the time scales that
you want based on the way humans
interact with the light switch.
So there's a lot
of development that
goes into figuring out the
right way to set this up.
The data that you collect
from a process like this,
how do we organize it?
This actually is not
transfer learning.
So I kind of lied
there a little bit.
This is strictly
language modeling.
It's a conversation between
the human and the lamp.
You say something, the lamp
says here's what you want.
And it's just extending
context window
like you'd see with a decoder
only kind of architecture
these days.
A chatbot kind of thing.
A human personal assistant.
Human assistant dialogue.
And you might also
suspect then that, well,
couldn't you let the lamp talk?
Yes.
You could absolutely
let it use other tokens.
And that is something which
is on the horizon for us.
In other words, how to determine
once the model is learned enough
and knows when you
want to hear it talk
and knows what you
want to hear it say,
which requires other smart
data collection currently
in development.
And there's three tags
here if you don't see it,
although what they
really are tokens
since they're integrated within
the language models vocabulary.
I want the lamp lit.
I want the lamp dark or
nothing, if no switch is
applied during transcription.
So one of the models looked
like that go into a lamp.
They're a little bit smaller
than that micro model
in terms of having a long
context window be the block
size.
They still use
these other features
like a radius, which
help them to do well
with only little data.
Those other context models.
And the embedding sizes around
50 or 100 and something.
And this is small enough
to fit on a microprocessor
on a CPU of a microprocessor,
including training, no GPU
whatsoever.
And the first time we ever
got the interaction right,
the right time scales
from no data whatsoever,
creating this data.
And 20 minutes of it was enough.
And you can see there's
loads of misspellings
here because the transcription
is not required to produce
known words, known tokens.
It's strictly character-based.
So you can say whatever
you want to say.
You can whistle.
And as long as wav2vec
thinks that's tokens,
it'll figure out
what to transcribe.
That's enough, 20
minutes of talking to it
to have it know pretty well
when you want the light on.
This is what the numbers look
like for that prediction.
And you see lots of zeros there.
But that's because there's
no positive instances yet
in the data until
you flip the switch,
there's nothing to predict.
Once there is enough
to predict, we
see an immediate jump
in the model's ability
to figure out whether
lamp should stay on or off
or nothing.
And while we trained this
first model, for example,
in 20 minutes on potato,
which is a really, really,
really small microprocessor,
it's incredibly frustrating
to utilize because the
processing time is a couple
seconds and it feels like
it's going somewhere,
even though the data is entirely
localized, there's no Wi-Fi,
there's no internet connection.
It just takes the model on
this tiny chip a minute--
not really a minute,
like a couple seconds
to flip the switch on because
it has to transcribe it,
interpret it, issue
the directive,
ask the operator to operate it.
And so part of what we're
doing is figuring out,
at what scale of microprocessing
do the models that we're
developing really make a good
real-time system that a user can
make use of?
Well, and as you can see,
the larger the model in terms
of hyperparameters and so forth,
the more performance it gets.
So we see these as potentially
useful in edge scenarios,
but not just for
operation, for training.
So go to Home depot, buy
a light switch, install it
in your house,
start talking to it.
But this isn't
really the stopping
point that we want to get to.
We want to eventually get
to the point of talk back.
We want to treat these as
language models that essentially
have a bit of U inside of them
that you can converse with.
And that's important to know
when the model is aware of what
you want to hear said.
In other words, it needs to know
what is a good thing to say back
to what you just said?
And the lamp has never
heard a lamp talk before.
So there are challenges
to figuring out the lamp's
role in conversation.
And choosing a lamp,
though, is arbitrary.
We don't have to make it
be a light bulb, which
goes on and off.
This could be a
controller for anything
which is a binary switch.
And you could imagine, like
others are looking at right now,
there's a lot of
opportunities with predicting
the action on your phone
that you want to take,
which thing you want to push.
And with a system like this,
micro-sizing on to your cell
phone for example,
assumes better hardware
than what we're already using,
but would be entirely localized,
including training.
But this is also
really just getting
to the point of feasibility.
It's not getting to the point of
a well optimized system, which
we're still developing.
There are in principle
different modifications
that we could make to the
self-attention layers, which
include traditional
self-attention parameters.
That's just one example.
Then there are updates
to the very naive scheme
that we have for
bit-cipher, the vectors
that we're using to
initialize our models.
And a lot of other minutiae
that need to be approached.
So this isn't really
work that's done.
It's a work in progress.
And in addition to
what I just described,
we're moving towards larger
models and evaluations that
compare better to modern
systems, which will eventually
come online.
We'll most likely participate in
this year's baby language model
challenge.
Although that challenge
assumes you're
working with a standard
architecture, which is already
developed for all of
the evaluative needs.
So there's a lot of work to do.
But that's really all I have
prepared for you to discuss
today in this conversation.
I've gone over a lot of details.
And if you'd like to
talk about any of these,
I'm certainly happy to.
Questions that you
might have as well.
And if you have
access to the slides,
there's some links to
the different papers
I've referenced.
That's all for today.
Thanks.
[APPLAUSE]
OK, so thanks, Jake,
for the great talk.
And now we'll have some
time for questions.
So if anybody here
has any questions,
feel free to raise
your hand and ask.
Otherwise, we'll go to
some questions on Slido.
Now some folks are
asking, so we'll
be posting the slides later.
But I've also pasted these
references in the Zoom
chat as well as Discord in
case anybody wants to see them.
I was wondering, in the
plots that you showed
for warm start
versus cold start,
does the cold start use
the modified self-attention
or the standard self-attention?
Yeah, sure.
So the question was in this
picture comparing warm starts
to cold starts.
What self-attention
was used here?
None.
This is strictly a
feedforward experiment,
where we take a
single layer and all
we do is feedforward with one
hot vectors from some context
window.
And concatenate them together.
And the general
property that you'll see
is by concatenating
vectors, there's
very little for attention to do.
Normally with a block, you're
adding the vectors together.
And that superposition of
the dimensions smears them.
And that's why self-attention
is needed in order
to weight that superposition.
So just the right one stick
out and it's not muddled.
If those vectors are
instead concatenated,
a weighting of those is
really just appealing
to the sensibilities
of the matrix above.
When they're
superimposed, there's
a lot to work on
since you're smearing
separate information together.
When the information
is already separated,
there's not that much
reweighting can do.
And in this case, there's
absolutely no reweighting
going on.
And what I've described
to you is really
just something
that's become very
clear from a lot of
small scale experiments
in between the models
that we've developed.
And moving towards
self-attention
took additional
time, and we didn't
have a solution for that layer
yet when this work was done.
I had a question in
regards to, so you're
doing this with on edge
controllers, right?
With what?
You're doing with on
edge controllers, right?
You're doing training
for on edge controllers.
So this could be for
IoT devices, right?
Could be.
And you talked about how
this all sorts of work
for image data, right?
Yeah.
Have you conducted any
tests with image data,
with these small
models for IoT devices
or do you plan to the future?
So image data work best on not
just feedforward architectures.
They have, for example,
convolutional things, bits
and pieces that
are useful to them.
And that means if we want to
apply some kind of a warm start,
for example, a
convolutional layer
to create a perform
an image classifier
or something that's
working with images,
we'd want to develop an
initialization for that layer
too.
It has weirder
activation functions,
which means we need to
branch out from softmax
as an activation function.
But surprisingly
similar convolution
is to a radial model.
It's really just saying
what's near where
I'm trying to create a feature.
So I would say yes, it
seems like it's something
that we could do.
But currently it's in
the phase of future work
that it fits in one bullet here.
At the bottom.
different layer types
need formal derivation
for warm starts.
So if we wanted to do
this kind of a thing
with a performance
architecture, we
would be probably
uniformly or randomly
initializing some
of those parameters
that we don't have
warm starts for yet.
And as a result, we would
receive a lot of noise
and where things are going.
And if we started to utilize
the activation functions,
whether it's even just
logistic activation,
a logistic activation is not
really fundamentally different
than a softmax activation.
So you might say,
for example, well,
why can't you just apply that to
a logistic function like a two
dimensional softmax?
And the reason is, is
because if we treat it
like a standard logistic, then
each dimension is independent.
Each dimension is trying
to predict the same thing.
And there's a lot more
questions about how
you can get different
information out
of different dimensions.
So that's a question that's
really worth spending time on,
in my opinion, separately.
And it's not the
first question that
makes a lot of what we've
developed practical.
One of the slides we had the
dialogue between the user.
And I'm wondering,
does that imply
there is a speech to text system
inside the microcontroller
housing?
So audio goes in.
And there's a process here,
which accepts that audio.
And it utilizes a
pre-trained wav2vet.
That's really just fitting a
need with a pre-trained model.
That's what we're
doing right now.
Although transcription
is something
that we would like to move
into in our future work
for the purposes of training
from scratch, because one
of the real benefits
of a system like this
is that it doesn't
come with any biases
from other people's
data aside from the fact
that there's a pre-trained
transcription system, which
means that it's pre-trained
towards whatever phonetics were
within the language
that was there
for pre-training in
the wav2vec algorithm.
So there is external
utility here coming
from a pre-trained model.
But the text itself
and the language model
that we're presenting
is only working
from what gets transcribed.
I have a follow-up on
my previous question.
You said that the
feedforward warm start
is independent of the
choice of self-attention.
Does that mean that
the warm start strategy
can be used for any network that
uses a feedforward layer, not
just PLNs but any LLM
or any other network?
Yeah.
So that's going back to the
warm start solution here.
And what it says is that in
terms of any layer beneath,
if you assume that those layers
parameters are what they are,
you're not going to update them.
And assuming that you know
what the targets for that layer
are, which for middle layers,
there are some questions
to be answered, then
this initialization
will do better than
random for softmax output.
That's really
important at this stage
if there's a softmax as
a part of the activation.
If there's not, then
more math, basically.
But the point at
which it becomes clear
should that whatever type
of prediction scenario
in, as long as you have
non-negative features
and a softmax for
activation, like
in this case with a single layer
or even two softmax layers,
whatever that's
doing on MNIST, you
can get a really
good initialization.
Doesn't have to be
linguistic data.
And this can be mixed data, too.
You could do an image
caption generation
system that has both
features from images and text
and warms them up with the
same solution with entirely
different data in two places.
Could you point out
which part of the process
requires the values
to be non-negative?
What happens when you put
a negative in a logarithm?
I'm not saying you
can't, but it's not
going to start making
probabilities for you
at the other end of the
softmax anytime fast.
So you have to start with a
different premise, essentially.
And that premise is something
that requires more derivation.
You'd want to assure
if you're going
to use a logarithm anywhere
or assume that inverse,
that you're able
to probably modify
every parameter
independently instead
of whole rows of parameters.
To get to a couple of questions
on Slido that folks asked.
The first is what's
the difference
in performance between
naive assignment
and optimized or omniscient
assignment for packing
tokens into bit vectors and
any experimental results?
What's the difference
in performance between--
Naive assignment and optimized
assignment for packing
tokens into bit vectors?
The performance differences
are going to be in speed.
The systems which utilize
packing for contexts
have at great length
gone to make sure
that information from different
portions of the context that
have nothing to
do with each other
don't bleed
information if you're
going to pack them together.
That creates a lot of
logistical challenges
in terms of defining models.
And it's still just doing the
regular self-attention thing.
So it's quadratic.
So if you have the same
length of context window,
it's going to be the
same computational cost.
However, if you pack all of
your small documents together,
they don't need the
whole context window
worth of quadratic comparisons.
And that's why you pack
something into the empty end.
I guess it should be over
here in your perspective.
But token or document
packing isn't exactly--
even though it's well
known as a mechanism
to make training
much more efficient.
In other words, you
only need fewer batches
if more documents
are packed together,
it's not something which is,
for example, entirely accepted
as a published accepted
form of pre-processing.
So what I would say is just
document packing is not
a correct model of context.
It is an efficiency, but
requires the same level
of quadratic comparison.
Whereas dynamically
batching and utilizing
a block size that is dynamic
preserves the model of context.
It does something that
is true to the objective
and unwavering in that.
And it reduces the complexity
for smaller documents.
But direct comparison
of the two is
something I have
not done because it
would require having that Oracle
and utilizing those algorithms.
And where they're used, they're
used with insanely big models,
which means we
would likewise have
to compare to insanely
big models to create
the same level of
expectation that people have
from packing in the future.
Great.
Thanks for your
detailed response.
We have a question
quickly that's
asking, are there any
implementations of sample
available that one
could experiment with?
Well, once we publish,
there will be.
But that requires a lot of
work on developing systems
for evaluation, since
the evaluation systems
rely upon standardized functions
within the architectures
that you're all very familiar
with, like GPT-2 that are easily
taken for granted.
Even though you do lots
of work and training them,
you have to do a lot of work in
creating those functions that
meet the needs of the
separate prediction tasks
and fine-tuning that
evaluations perform.
All right, great.
Makes sense.
I think we're pretty
much out of time.
So T thanks, Jake,
for the great talk.
And thanks for coming to
another lecture, all of you.